

Phone: 01667329537

Email:

doanhoanle1594@gmail.com

Address: 7 Tan Hung, district 5, HCMC

Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work.

#### **SKILLS**

Time management

Work under pressure

**Microsoft Office** 

Teamwork

Presentation

**Problem Solving** 

English

Communication

# LE DOAN HOAN

#### CAREER GOAL

I have a desire to apply for a job or intership job to experience the things learned at school in real life as well as gain new knowledge. I am not afraid of failure so when I'm determined to do something I put my whole ability, responsibility and dedication to bring the most complete results. The development of the company, the satisfaction of customers and the improvement of myself are my top priority in my career. With all my energy and my up coming experience with the company, I hope to be a core employee of the company in 3 years. It is the motivation for me to become an expert in the field that I am pursuing and contribute to help the company reach new heights.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **2015 – 2016: Self – employee**

- Sold comestics and accessories
- Learned how to promote my products and make them attractive to customers. The business alone helped me develop my independence and creativity. And in my one year of business has brought me 13 million interest

## 10-2015: Salesperson – book fair of Nha Nam Bookstore

- Introduced and sold new books to customers
- I learned how to recommend good and interesting books for each type of customers so as to meet their psychological demands and then satisfy them. Sold 40 books in the 3 day bookfair

#### 2014-2015: PB

• Mastered skills of drawing people's attention to the products such as shampoo and cake

#### 2013-2014: Tutor

- Taught secondary and high school students
- Delivered well prepared lessons to students
- Learned how to convey knowledge to my students in an easy- to- understand way Education.

# **EDUCATION**

2013-2018: Medicine & Pharmacy University in Ho Chi Minh City – Faculty of Pharmacy

## **ACTIVITIES**

## 1/2017-3/2017: Bootcamp 2017 - Medicine & Pharmacy University

- Member of Board of Organization
- Got the participation of over 1,000 people

#### **Volunteer – Cong bang Y te Program**

 Free medical examination and free drug supply to the poor in the West of Viet Nam

#### **Volunteer – Green Summer 2015 – MER-COV propaganda matrix**

• Spread knowledge of how to prevent MER-COV disease

**Volunteer – Green Summer 2014 – Dak Nong Province Volunteer** 

Xuan Tinh Nguyen Program 2014 - Ben Tre Province

# **Volunteer - Lam Quang Pogoda 2014**

• Organized events for over 100 soliatry elders every event

11 - 2013: Folk dancing for Le Ket Nghia - Duoc Khoa